Good morning, Hinata.
Good morning... Wha— Bell?!
Why are you naked?!
Because it's Sunday.
That doesn't explain anything!
Before we eat breakfast,
how about... you—eat—me?
What are you doing?
Meddling again?!
We would have no need to meddle
if you simply behaved yourself.
Aw, lighten up, Cecil.
Keep a close eye on them, May.
Remember, we didn't come to
this world for the fun of it.
M'kay!
Those clothes... You're going to work?
Yes. I got called in today.
Anyways, I'm heading out.
Cecil sure is busy...
I was tasked with monitoring
Mariabell for one month...
And somehow, I ended up at a hot spring.
So, this is what they mean by "luxurious"...
Ya-hoo!
May! Can't you be quieter?
Aw, but we get this place
all to ourselves today.
Well, be that as it may...
If we had a choice with the reservation,
then we should've booked co-ed.
Hinata! Come over to our side!
Th-That's against the rules!
Quit bothering Lord Hinata.
C'mon, Cecil, don't be such a grump.
Give me some space, May!
You're pushing it.
Shouldn't you be thanking me right now?
I was the one who got us
into this place, remember?
With over 100,000 subscribers,
welcome to MayMay's Parallel Universe!
Celebrating 100,000 Subscribers!!
MayMay's Parallel Universe!
We get to stay at this swanky
hot spring resort
'cause of my streaming sponsorship!
And I'm grateful for that, but...
Hi—na—ta!
I see you!
B-Bell?!
What are you hiding?!
Let me see everything!
If you won't come over here,
then I'll just have to—
Get over here!
Owie!
Ouch...
It's been a while since I've had
a long soak in the tub...
You're always using the shower at the house.
Yes, well...
This is going to take all night...
It's back and forth between work and home...
with no break in between...
In a way, it's even more exhausting
than fighting demons.
Hmph. If it sucks so much,
you should just go back to our world.
Excuse me?
Calm down. You're just cranky
because you're hungry.
Let's go have some dinner and relax!
This is amazing!
I've only ever seen a spread
like this on TV!
Is it really on the house?
This seems extravagant for
an online streamer...
I'm not just going to eat it.
I have to review it, too!
That reminds me!
You guys should help me with my stream!
Huh?
I'll put a filter over your faces.
Hinata, you can be the cameraman!
MayMay's Parallel Universe
MayMay's Parallel Universe is live
She's streaming right now?!
Yoo-hoo! It's MayMay's Parallel Universe!
May the demi-human here,
ready to make my viewers smile!
I have some first-time guests
with me today!
H-Hello...
it started
i'm here! lol
sexy and cute lol
blond yukata beauty lol
blond lool
Hi there...
the guests lool
blond!!!!
they're gorgeous!
May has the coolest friends
are they from another world too?
i like the dark-haired one
they nervous??
what's she doing today?
She looks... a lot like Bell.
This hotel has an incredible
hot spring and food,
but the specialty around these parts is...
Ta-da!
What is that stuff?
It's oden!
Oh, I know!
Since we've got all this good food,
why don't we have an eating contest?
I saw a comedian on TV
do it the other day!
No. It isn't polite to play with your food.
Besides, it's insulting to the people
who made it for us.
Always so serious...
Then I guess we'll just eat it like normal!
I'll have this one!
Smells yummy!
Ooh, the bonito stock gives it
so much flavor!
And that broth really hits the spot!
Have some, you guys!
Right.
In that case, I think I'll try the sausage.
Here ya go!
Er, I can do it—
It's fine! Open wide!
Hot—!
C'mon, put it in your mouth!
I'm working on it.
It's all over your face!
Jeez, it's sticky...
Should I lick it clean for you?
Hey!
H-Help...!
That was kinda lewd...
I'm sorry for accidentally
ending the stream...
No worries!
I let everyone know what happened.
The important part is that we had fun.
It's all good!
How can you say that?!
I'm sweaty.
Should we hop in the bath again?
I had a blast on stream!
Hey, May?
What's up?
What made you decide to
become a streamer?
I wanted to make people smile.
I feel drained
This place is peaceful 'cause
there aren't any demons...
I'm bored all the time
...but lots of the people here
are burnt-out and struggling.
I wanted to make people happy
like when we defeated
the Demon Lord back home.
And that's when...
Magical Girl Idols Channel
Hang in there!
Don't give up!
Follow your dreams!
Tomorrow is another day!
I was introduced to streaming.
I like being surrounded by smiling faces,
so I want to make as many
people smile as I can!
You found a great job,
one you can be passionate about.
But my job is a lot of fun, too.
Really? It seems hard...
It's tough but rewarding.
Watching you and Mariabell
frolicking about in this world...
I forgot about my mission and
immersed myself in my work.
Perhaps I, too, began enjoying it here
without even realizing it.
This world is tons of fun!
And I feel like Hinata smiles more here, too!
Perhaps it's because he's no longer
burdened by heroic duty.
Lord Hinata seems more pleasant
than before, more human.
Speaking of which... where is Lord Hinata?
He said he was gonna
take a bath in his room...
Mariabell is missing, too...
Lord Hinata is in danger!
They even have huge, fancy tubs
in the rooms...
This hotel is nice.
Ah, just the two of us at last!
B-Bell?!
I thought you went to the open-air bath with—
I'm not interested in being
somewhere you're not.
That includes the bath.
You can't!
We shouldn't be in here together—
Aw... But if I get out now,
I might catch a cold.
Besides, I wanted to talk to you alone.
This is my very first vacation in this world...
Fine...
But the whole point of this trip
is to cheer up Miss Cecil, isn't it?
I couldn't care less about that.
Oh, come on. It's just me here, Bell.
You don't have to act tough.
The truth is, you were worried about
Miss Cecil, weren't you?
I-I was not!
It's just... In the other world,
the only humans who didn't look down
on dark elves were you...
and her.
If she isn't feeling well,
it'll throw me out of whack, too.
That's not very honest.
You want me to be honest?
There is something that's
been bothering me...
Earlier... you saw Cecil's boobs, didn't you?
Huh? Th-That whole thing
was just an accident...
So, you did see them.
The only boobs you're allowed to
look at in this world are mine.
The only man who's allowed to
look at my boobs is you.
You know you're special to me, right?
Y-Yeah...
If you said another pair of boobs
were better than mine,
I would probably massacre
every woman on this planet.
I want you to be addicted to my boobs,
so much so that you're
indifferent to all other boobs.
Jeez, she's intense...
Hey, Hinata? I'm hungry.
Huh? Then should we stop by the store?
If we go now, we might—
That's not what I meant.
I want to devour you, Hinata.
B-Bell...
Are you feeling any better?
No, Bell, this trip was for—
She's fine now.
So isn't it your turn to relax
and let yourself go?
If you keep doing that, I...
What are you doing?!
Miss Cecil!
Meddling again?!
I was only coaxing mini-Hinata
out of his shell!
Oh, you were cheering Hinata up?
In that case, let's all lift his spirits!
Shield your eyes!
Now we can all take a bath together!
Cannonball!
My first vacation with Hinata in this world
and we still didn't do it...
Now, now. It was a nice hotel.
Yeah! And we had a total blast!
Do you feel more rested?
Yes.
I think I'm going to cut down on
my workload a little from now on.
Oh yeah? Good to hear.
Too bad you didn't make yourself sick
and have to go back home!
I'll leave as soon as I'm certain
you aren't going to cause any problems.
Officially, I've been tasked with
monitoring the two of you.
However...
On a personal level, I'm rooting for you guys.
I feel the same way!
Th-Thank you.
I knew you'd throw me out of whack!